

#### **GET IN TOUCH!**

#### Mobile:

+91-6265992722

#### **Email:**

suneelyadavbilai2017@gmail.com

## **SKILLS**

- Data Entry
- Computer Operating
- Data Processing
- Back Office
- Office Assistance
- Sales
- Sales Management
- Tally ERP
- Billing
- Excel
- Financial Analysis
- Marketing
- Team Lead Account Manager
- Reception Manager
- Youtube
- Social Media
- Insurance Sales
- Administration

# **LANGUAGES KNOWN**

Hindi ( Both )

## **TEST RANKS**

- TOEFL : 70

# **Suneel Yaday**

#### **RESUME SUMMARY**

As a dedicated professional with experience in sales, team leadership, and data analysis, I strive to excel in roles that allow me to leverage my skills in sales management, financial analysis, and team handling. Committed to continuous improvement and achieving success in challenging environments.

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Current Location Ahmedabad
Date of Birth June 12, 2002

Male

### **EDUCATION**

#### **Graduation**

Course B.A ( Arts&Humanities )

College Shri Krishna University Chhatarpur
Course D.C.A ( diploma in computer application )

College Makhanlal Chaturvedi Rashtriya Patrakarita Vishwavidyalaya, Bhopal,

Bhopal

Score 77%

Schooling Class XII Class X
Board Name Madhya Pradesh Madhya Pradesh

MediumHindiHindiYear of Passing20202018Score61%60%

## **INTERNSHIPS**

### Motherson | September 2021 - August 2023

- Good my experience and skills improve

## **PROJECTS**

Job analysis at HDB FINANCIAL SERVICES | Home loan, proparty loans, personal loan, Business loan, | November 2023 - May 2024

- Conducted Job analysis by contacting data about three levels of empbyees viz teller sales officer and team leader.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

HDB Financial Services | June 2023 - May 2024

- Team leader :Sales manager

Motherson | May 2021 - May 2023 - Computer Operator:Computer operator

Fino Payments Bank | March 2020 - April 2021

- Sales Officer:Marchent accounts sales

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- All rounder in B.A
- All rounder in school